var miscQList = [
  {
    Question: "What AR level is required to ascend a character from 70 to 80?",
    A: "30",
    B: "35",
    C: "40",
    D: "50",
    ANS: "C",
  },
  {
    Question: "All of the following are combat events EXCEPT",
    A: "Hyakunin Ikki",
    B: "Vagabond Sword",
    C: "Seize the Day",
    D: "Hypostatic Symphony",
    ANS: "C",
  },
  {
    Question: "What is the average primogems (total) a player can get in a new Genshin Event?",
    A: "180",
    B: "320",
    C: "420",
    D: "640",
    ANS: "C",
  },
  {
    Question: "Which of the following Archon Quests does NOT feature the Traveler's twin?",
    A: "For a Tomorrow Without Tears",
    B: "A Soul Set Apart",
    C: "Memories of Inteyvat",
    D: "Omnipresence Over Mortals",
    ANS: "D",
  },
  {
    Question: "This Co-Op event was Genshin Impact's first ever event that released in Patch 1.0",
    A: "Unreconciled Stars",
    B: "Elemental Crucible",
    C: "Vagabond Sword",
    D: "Hyakunin Ikki",
    ANS: "B",
  },
  {
    Question: "Which of the following is the name of Xiangling's auto attack?",
    A: "Dough-Fu",
    B: "Guoba Attack",
    C: "Chef's Secret",
    D: "Crossfire",
    ANS: "A",
  },
  {
    Question: "Xingqiu's burst, Guhua Sword: Raincutter, requires how much energy to use?",
    A: "40",
    B: "60",
    C: "80",
    D: "90",
    ANS: "C",
  },
  {
    Question: "This banner made the most sales in Genshin Impact over a 3-week period.",
    A: "Klee",
    B: "Raiden Shogun",
    C: "Yoimiya",
    D: "Venti",
    ANS: "B",
  },
  {
    Question: "This character demo is the most popular demo on the Genshin Impact YouTube Channel",
    A: "Zhongli",
    B: "Raiden Shogun",
    C: "Venti",
    D: "Xiangling",
    ANS: "A",
  },
  {
    Question: "Should Twitch Chat use their FREE Twitch Prime Subscription by clicking on the purple 'Subscribe' button below",
    A: "yes",
    B: "yes",
    C: "yes",
    D: "yes",
    ANS: "A",
  },
  ];
